sitepal.com 2012-12-30

# Oddcast - Privacy Policy

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

Oddcast recognizes that our customers value their right to privacy and want to be assured that any personal information that they provide to us will be used in accordance with their wishes. Oddcast is committed to ensuring that you are fully informed as to how your personal information will be used and that it will be kept secure.

  1. What information do we collect?
  2. Purpose for which we use Information
  3. Sharing of Information which Third Parties
  4. Security
  5. Cookies
  6. Links
  7. Chat Rooms and Newsgroups
  8. Children
  9. Access, Modification and Accuracy of Information
  10. Retention and Storage of Information
  11. Change of Privacy Policy
  12. Business Transfers
  13. Acceptance of Terms
  14. Contact Us

**1\. What information do we collect?**

Oddcast may collect personal information from you relating both to your identity and personal preferences. Oddcast will endeavor only to collect such information as is necessary for the stated purpose for which we are collecting the information. For example, if you purchase the Oddcast service, we will require your personal information so that we can send you your login information and obtain payment.

There are a number of different ways that we may collect personal information from you: 

_Communications from you_  
You may contact us providing your name and contact details and any other personal information contained in your message.

_Customer Support_  
You may contact us in respect of technical assistance you require in respect of our products or information that you would like to receive relating to our products.

_Email/Direct mail campaigns_  
From time to time we may contact you directly by mail, email or telephone informing you about upgrades, new products, promotions or special offers that you may be interested in.

_Newsletters_  
We may send out newsletters to our customers providing them with articles and information which we believe may be of interest to you.

_Registration of Products_  
Upon registration, you will be asked to provide certain information so that we can record you as an owner of the Oddcast service to help us in providing you with service and information. We require that you provide certain contact information.

_Purchases_  
If you wish to purchase from our SitePalTM Store, we will require sufficient information to complete the purchase including your credit card information and your contact details.

_Surveys_  
From time to time we may conduct surveys in respect of our products and services. Participation is optional.

_Aggregate Information_  
Whenever you enter our website, our web server automatically collects and aggregates information in respect of your visit. This information includes URLs or domains of referring websites, browser type, operating system, the pages that you access and the date and time of your visit. In general this aggregate information will not identify you personally. If we do correlate such information to you, we will treat it in accordance with this policy.

**2\. Purposes for which we use information**

Oddcast may gather personally identifiable information about you, ONLY if you voluntarily choose to provide it yourself (for example: while submitting certain forms in or through the Website, or while registering to the Oddcast Pricing section). If you choose not to provide required information, Oddcast may not be able to comply with your request or provide certain services.

_Product Registration_  
Information you provide upon registration will be used to keep a record of your purchases and will assist in providing assistance if you contact our customer support service. We will also use this information to inform you of any upgrades, new products or promotions that may be of interest to you.

_Product Purchases_  
When you purchase from our SitePalTM Store or directly from our Customer Services department, we will use your information to process payment and send you your login information.

_Information in respect of Oddcast Products_  
It is important for us to receive feedback from our customers and any features they would like to see in future products. We may contact you to ask you about our products and also to inform you of upgrades, technical issues, promotions and new products that you may be interested in.

_Internal Analysis_  
We may use the information you provide us with for our own internal statistical and analytical purposes, to evaluate and profile customers, including customer preferences and purchasing trends, which we may use for marketing purposes and in respect of operations and development.

_Updating information_  
We may contact you to ensure that the information we have in our records is still correct and to add additional information to complete your profile.

**3\. Sharing of information with third parties**

We may use outside vendors to process payment from customers.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other provides of products or services, advertisers, other web-sites or any other third-party which may be involved in or linked to Oddcast's business. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linking information. Your personal information may be subject to different privacy practices exercised by other providers, and Oddcast is not responsible for the privacy practices exercised by any such providers. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit these providers individually to learn more about how they handle privacy.

_Legal Disclaimer_  
Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required to do so by law or necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Website.

**4\. Security**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is stored and maintained in a secure environment. We have implemented procedures to ensure that your information is only made available to such designated staff as necessary to carry out the stated purposes that we have communicated to you.

_SSL Encryption_  
Order information received by the SitePalTM Store, including credit card information, is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). This ensures that your information is secure as it is sent over the Internet to our server.

**5\. Cookies**

We may make use of "cookies" on our website. A cookie is a small text file that can be placed and stored on your computer's hard disc when you visit a website for record keeping purposes. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from a user's computer (other than the contents of the cookie); rather, it is an identifier used by the Web site that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same server to identify the computer and subsequently to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of a site based on information stored on the host server. Therefore, cookies only identify the user's computer to the Web site which may correlate other information, including personally identifying information, with the cookie.

We use cookies to allow us to automate access and the data entry functions of our website such as to correlate online ordering information for purchases you may make while at the website (if any), tailor our website to your preferences or interests, or customize promotions or marketing. In addition, cookies allow us to track use of our website to determine those areas which are useful or popular and those that are not thereby enabling us to improve and update our website effectively.

Banners served from the Oddcast site do not drop cookies for re-targeting or tracking purposes.

Most web browsers can either alert you to the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. If you are not sure how to do this or whether you have this option you should consult the documentation that accompanied your web browser. You should be aware that if you elect not to accept cookies, some parts of the website may not function properly or permit access.

**6\. Links**

We may offer links from our website to other websites which may be hosted by our partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and Oddcast makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

**7\. Chat rooms and newsgroups**

Oddcast's website may have chat rooms, newsgroups, or other forums which permit individuals to interact online. Any information you transmit online in such forums will be made public and Oddcast cannot control nor is it responsible for the use any third parties may make of such information.

**8\. Children**

This site is a general audience site which is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children who are under the age of 13. In order to ensure compliance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information to this site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

**9\. Access, modification and accuracy of information**

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the information that we receive from you is accurate and kept up to date. You have the right to access your information to verify the information that we have collected in respect of you. You also have the right to request that your information be modified or deleted, including any changes to any consents that you may have given in respect of us contacting you relating to information that you receive from us. You may also ask at any time that your preferences as to the type of communications that you receive from us are modified in order to stop receiving them or to be added to our mailing list. We will endeavor to deal with all such requests for access and modifications in a timely manner. We will not be able to comply with requests in respect of information that we may have archived as part our business operations.

**10\. Retention and storage of information**

We will retain your information for a reasonable time to permit us to use it for the purposes that we have communicated to you.

We may use the services of third party companies to physically collect and store your information on our behalf. Any such companies will have to comply with the terms of this policy.

**11\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may change the terms of this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect our practices and provide greater protection for your information. Any change to this policy will be clearly displayed on this website. Any changes to this policy will not have retrospective effect. Information collected by us will be dealt within accordance with the provisions of our policy which were in effect at the time of collection.

**12\. Business transfers**

The information that is collected by Oddcast is considered to be an asset. In the event that Oddcast, any affiliated company, division or portions of its assets are acquired by another company, such information may be one of the transferred assets. We will take reasonable steps to place a notification of such a transfer on our website.

**13\. Acceptance of terms**

By using our services, accessing our website or purchasing our products you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this policy.

**14\. Contact us**

Any requests for access to your information, modification of your information or questions in respect of this policy should be sent to the following email address [privacy@oddcast.com](mailto:privacy@oddcast.com).
